<root>
    <id>19</id>
    <title>Guy</title>
    <post>
        <p>I am a handsome 30 year old Blue and Gold Macaw who is very much loved but looking for a new wonderful, warm and quiet home as I get older.</p> <p>Like all parrots I really benefit from a good daily routine, with a goodnight sleep of 12 hours. Luckily for me my routine involves several naps throughout the day and taking myself away for some quiet time when I feel I need it. I like most foods providing they are full of flavour, so I may put your chop making skills to the test. I really enjoy a variety of foods and having some fruit and vegetable snacks throughout the day. I’m not a huge fan of parrot toys, instead I would much rather play with cardboard boxes and wood, so you will need to know what wood is safe for parrots and have access to plenty of it for me to destroy.</p> <p>My new home should be an adult only home, ideally with a male as my main caretaker. </p> <p>If you can provide me with a loving home where I will receive lots of attention, a good routine and the tastiest food then please complete an application for and one of the team from Parrot Trust Scotland will get in touch.</p>
    </post>
    <author>IainPTS</author>
    <date>2020-10-24</date>
    <imagelocation>Guy.jpg</imagelocation>
    <id>18</id>
    <title>Billie</title>
    <post>
        <p>Hello, my name is Billie. I am a stunning Congo African Grey in my 20’s. I am looking for a new home where I can be the centre of attention.</p> <p>I really am a gorgeous bird, if I do say so myself. I am very easy going and I am happy spending my days whisliting away, playing with my toys and eating some good food. I will try just about anything you give me, if I don’t try it at first I likely will in a day or so. I particularly love my chop in the morning and pellets for my dinner.</p> <p>I would do much better in a home where my main carer is male as I am much calmer around men.</p> <p>If you think you can provide me with all the love, attention and great food I could ever ask for then please complete an application form and one of the humans from Parrot Trust Scotland will get in touch.</p>
    </post>
    <author>IainPTS</author>
    <date>2020-10-24</date>
    <imagelocation>Billie.jpg</imagelocation>
    <id>16</id>
    <title>Maisie</title>
    <post>
        <p>Hello, my name is Maisie, I am a gorgeous young 10 year blue and gold macaw.</p> <p>I am currently looking for a new home where I can be absolutely spoiled and be the pampered princess. I am a gorgeous girl and just want a forever home with all the love and attention you have to offer. </p> <p>You will notice I pluck my feathers, however people say this makes me even more special. It is just a habit I have got myself in to. I love my food, nice warm porridge, occasional boiled egg, fruit, tidymix but I sometimes need a bit of persuading with veggies and will throw them if I am in a bit of a strop! And I really don’t like carrots much! I do like some nice treats like brazils, walnuts and almonds.</p> <p>I love being out my cage with plenty of space as I can fly! I love to stretch my wings! But I am also happy sitting watching the TV and listening to music! I love music and try to join in when my foster mum sings to me! It makes me giggle too. </p> <p>My ideal home would have no children, as I am not a fan of them at all and I would rather be with people who have experience with macaws or other large parrots. I especially like females as I love to play with their hair. I do tolerate other animals though especially the ones that bark. I also don’t mind the company of other birds who look like me (although none of them will be as smart as me..just saying..)</p> <p>If you think you can offer me all the time, attention and love you have to offer as well as a great diet and be willing to put up with my usual macaw tendencies then please complete an application form. After that one of the human folk from Parrot Trust Scotland will get in touch. Claw wave for now!</p>
    </post>
    <author>IainPTS</author>
    <date>2020-09-18</date>
    <imagelocation>Maisie.jpg</imagelocation>
</root>